{
    "id": "85e0ec5bf43c45d686d7aa1bd36e53c1",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "…………………. fast, I managed to catch up with him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Running",
                "Having ran",
                "Being run"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is …………………… loyal to cheat on her.",
            "description": "This sentence means the same as 'He is so loyal that he will not / cannot cheat on her.'",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. the doctors tried their best, they could not save the patient.",
            "description": "Although is a conjunction connecting two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "Despite",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "James, ………………………. works abroad, is coming home next week.",
            "description": "That cannot be used to refer people in non-identifying relative clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "who",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… their best efforts, they could not save him.",
            "description": "Despite is a preposition use it before a noun or ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "Though",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The higher you go, ………………………… it gets.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the cool",
                "the cold",
                "colder",
                "the colder"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "They fought to the finish …………………………, they could not win.",
            "description": "However is a transitional adverb it does not connect two clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "despite",
                "however"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "If the manager finds out, we ………………………… in trouble.",
            "description": "In the first conditional, use a simple present tense in the if-clause and will + first form of the verb in the main clause. ",
            "answers": [
                "will be",
                "would be",
                "would have been"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I would rather you ………………….. me alone.",
            "description": "After would rather, we use a simple past with present or future meaning. ",
            "answers": [
                "leave",
                "left",
                "had left"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You had better not …………………. him up.",
            "description": "Use the bare infinitive after had better. ",
            "answers": [
                "woke",
                "wake",
                "woken"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not ………………………….. so hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "used to work",
                "used to working",
                "used working",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It is time she ……………………… her mistake.",
            "description": "Use a simple past after it is time. ",
            "answers": [
                "realizes",
                "realized",
                "has realized"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}